abhishek chandrasekhar

- Atlanta, GA
- 404.890.0064
- me@abhchand.me
- abhchand.me

Hello!

I'm an engineering manager with almost a decade of experience in building enterprise software.

My experience ranges from building applications from the ground up to managing teams and scaling applications that serve over 25 million people.

EXPERIENCE



Glassbreakers

Engineering Manager San Francisco, CA | 2015 - 2018

As a lead engineer for almost 3 years, I was the primary developer and owner of the vast majority of app features.

I managed an engineering team across the United States ■ and Nigeria ■ and also played a large role in serving as both Product Manager and contributing designer.



Opower

Implementation Engineer San Francisco, CA | 2012 - 2015

Responsible for launching, configuring, deploying, and maintaining Opower products across 100+ clients

Chief engineer of first Peak Time Rebate product serving 1.5 million Baltimore customers Lead the largest ever Implementation for 22 million households in Tokyo, Japan Asia-Pacific delivery team lead with a portfolio of 5 strategic clients

2013

2014

2015



Capgemini

Business Analyst Atlanta, GA | 2010 - 2012

Conducted maintenance, testing, and development of enterprise systems for Telecom partners

Worked on Billing, Credit, and Collections systems for a Telecom provider in New England Implemented an iPhone product launch with POS / Ordering system for a Wireless Provider in Alaska

2010

2011

2012

EDUCATION



Georgia Tech

Bachelor Science
Electrical Engineering

Master of Science

Industrial Engineering

SKILLS

See examples of projects I've worked on at abhchand.me/projects

Frameworks	Non-technical	Automation	Databases
ruby / rails	people management	ansible	postgres
java / spark / spring	product management	chef	mysql
reactJS	design	puppet	hadoop
python / django			elasticsearch